Guide to the Lorraine García-Nakata papers M2056
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Lorraine García-Nakata papers
circa 1980-2015
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
García-Nakata, Lorraine
M2056
15 Linear Feet (36 boxes, 1 map folder)
Personal papers of California artist and arts administrator Lorraine García-Nakata.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Note that material must be requested at least 36 hours in advance of intended use. Audiovisual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This collection was purchased by Stanford University, Special Collections in 2015-2016.
Scope and Contents
Lorraine García-Nakata is a California-based visual artist who has exhibited locally, nationally, and internationally. She was born in 1950 in Yuba City, California, and is a third-generation descendant of Mexican immigrants. She is also deeply involved with art administration, including work with the Mexican Museum, Yerba Buena Center and Children’s Book Press, and serving on the SF Arts Commission.
The Lorraine García-Nakata collection encompasses her work as a visual artist, musician, writer, community/arts cultural specialist, and arts administrator. Materials include art catalogues, awards, day planners, photographs, slides, administrative files, meeting minutes, artwork, media, and other material. There is also a great deal of art by other artists (some of which by students of hers), others are posters silkscreens serving as art, event publicity, and political and cultural statements.
Mexican American artists; Arts -- Management; García-Nakata, Lorraine
- Administrative Files - Desk Stuff
  - College of Creative Arts Development Priorities (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - Plan - CA (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Pres. Weekly Reports (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Contact Report Info (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Tides Foundation (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Monthly Reports & Contact Reports (Box 1, Folder 7-9)
  - Management Personnel Plan Performance Review (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Ann Rockefeller Roberts (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - William Randolph Hearst, III (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Morrison 50th Anniversary (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Changing Channels March 22-23, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - '04 - '05 Communications Directory (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - SFSU Material (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Marcus, Budget (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Gerald Huth (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Will Fountain (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Modems Kege (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - LGN Conflict Interest (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Material (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Time Sheets (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Lewie Shule (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - California State Summer School for the Arts (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - California Arts Council (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Arts and Humanities Guidelines (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Material (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - N.S. de Guadalupe (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - The Mexican Museum Mission Statement (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - 4 Floppy disks (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Notebook (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - PEN (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Writings (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Bridges, Translations and Change: The Arts as Infrastructure in Twenty First Century America (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Center for the Study of Art & Community (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - AIR-Mission Cult. Ctr. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Marin Community Foundation (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - L. Garcia Nakata (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Lorraine Garcia Nakata (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Bones Resume (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - LGN Statements (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Material (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Letters of Support (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Eva (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Peer Review Info (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - CSSSA Material (Box 4, Folder 11-13)
  - Miscellaneous Pin (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - To Interim/Trustee Transition Written Report/Info. (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous Material (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Interviews Room for the Dead Dia de los Muertos (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Pachell W. Rigney Meeting: 11/17/1998 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Employment Information (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Letters of Support (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Mexican Museum Advisory (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Museum Accreditation (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Lists (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Facility + Operations (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Education (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Material (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Dallas Conference June 5-7 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Letters of Gratitude (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Bay Area Small Business (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Erin Morgan (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Conservation Issues Collection and Conservation (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous Contracts (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Acquisitions (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - New Facility (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Levi Strauss Proposal - Tech. Asst. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Birthday Card (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - The non-profit's Guide to Creating an Effective Governing Board (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - News from Native California (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Open Meeting Laws California Attorney General's Office 1989 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Opening the Museum (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Dia de los Muertos Research Info (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - The 2000 Partnership (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - IDRS Training Workshops in Communication, Decision-making and Dispute Resolution (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Speakers Youth Task Force Resource Handbook 1995 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Pamphlets (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Museum Studies are they doing their job? (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Center for the Arts Yerba Buena Gardens (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Walker Art Center (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Various Articles (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - The Stress of Organizational Change (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Paul Chaat Smith (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Material (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Admininstrative Files- Contracts/Projects
  - Northern California World Dance Directory (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Museum Building Report (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Mexican Museum File (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Riverbend Entertainment (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Velocity Circus Troupe (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Rob McKay (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Potential Thank-You Cards (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Material (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Return to: Lorraine Garcia-Nakata (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Cancer Detection Section (Box 27, Folder 7-8)
  - Wedding Reception Emma and Peter (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Reimbursments (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Galeria Anniversary Catalogue (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Oakland Museum (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Material (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Castellano Fund (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - City College Contract (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Nametags (Box 29)
- San Francisco Arts Commission, 2008-2011
  - S.F. Arts Commission Meeting Minutes September 17, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Meeting Minutes 2008 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Inside/Out Fifth Edition 2006 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Meeting Minutes June-August 2008 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous Material (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Meeting Minutes July - October 2008 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Meeting Minutes September - November 2008 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Meeting Minutes November 2008 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Meeting Minutes 2008 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Meeting Minutes November 2008 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Meeting Minutes December 2008 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Meeting Minutes January 2009 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Meeting Minutes January 2009 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Meeting Minutes January - February 2009 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Meeting Minutes January 2009 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Meeting Minutes 2009 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Meeting Minutes January - March 2009 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Post-Inauguration Catalog (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Street Artists Committee March 11, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Visual Arts Committee March 18, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Meeting Minutes Feb. - March 2009 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Meeting Minutes Feb. - March 2009 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Meeting Minutes May 2009 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Meeting Minutes May 27, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Minutes March - May 2009 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Material (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Meeting Minutes June - August 2009 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Cultural Equity Overview of Grantmaking Process (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Meeting Minutes May - September 2009 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Material (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Meeting Minutes May - October 2009 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Minutes September 8, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Meeting Minutes October, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - S.F. Arts Commission June - December 2009 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - S.F Arts Commission June - December 2009 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - 2009 Salsa & Latin Jazz Calendar (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - S.F. Symphony Playbill November 2009 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - S.F. Arts Commission January - December 2009 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Treasures January - June 2010 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - S.F. Arts Commission January - February 2010 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Cultural Equity Grants (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - S.F. Arts Commission January - April 2010 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - S.F. Arts Commission February - April 2010 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - S.F. Arts Commission (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Agenda July 21,2010 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - S.F. Arts Commission April - August 2010 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Miscellaneous Material (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Miscellaneous Material (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Miscellaneous Material (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Miscellaneous Material (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Miscellaneous Material (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Miscellaneous Material (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Miscellaneous Material (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Material 2010 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Material 2011 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Material 2010 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Material (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Academy of Arts University October 2010 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Material (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Strategic Plan Status Report (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Meeting of the Full Arts Commission Minutes 2010 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Meeting of the Full Arts Commission Minutes 2010 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - S.F. Arts Commission District Report 2010 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Miscellaneous Material (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Miscellaneous Material (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Minutes 2010 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Meeting of the Full Arts Commission 2011 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Meeting of the Full Arts Commission 2011 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - S.F. Performances Dance 2011 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Miscellaneous Material (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Meeting of the Full Arts 2011 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Julie W. Chang February 2011 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Community, Arts, Education, and Grants Committee (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Material (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - S.F. Committee Minutes 2011 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Minutes 2011 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - American Sabor (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Minutes 2011 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - S.F. Commission Miscellaneous Material (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Miscellaneous Material (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Visual Arts Committee Agenda & Minutes (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Miscellaneous Material (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Minutes 2011 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Miscellaneous Material (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - S.F. Arts Commission Miscellaneous Material (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Children's Book Press (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Mexican Museum & Yerba Buena Center
  - Mexican Museum binder (Box 37, Folder 3-4)
    Scope and Contents
    Includes photographs, slides, design drafts, computer diskettes, etc.
  - Yerba Buena Center educational materials produced by LGN (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Mexican Museum Schematic Design Submittal, Legorreta Arquitectos, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - The Mexican Museum Overview of Organizational Activities (Box 15, Folder 6-8)
  - The Mexican Museum Retail Business Plan Nov. 17, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Shah Kawasaki Material (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Agreement For Operation of Cultural Facilities (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Center for the Arts Yerba Buena Gardens (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Center for the Arts Annual Report 1993-1994 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Floppy Disk (Box 16, Folder 5-8)
  - Mexican Museum Miscellaneous Material (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Center for the Arts at Yerba Buena Gardens (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Center for the Arts Yerba Buena Gardens Material (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - The Mexican Cultural Heritage Gardens and Plaza Project (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Grants for the Arts Performing, Visual, Media and Literary Arts Organizations Application Checklist (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Center for the Arts Yerba Buena Gardens Annual Report 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - A Museum Guide to Copyright and Trademark (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - The Mexican Museum Part III: Narrative Case Statement (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Professional Practices in Art Museums (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Maya Advertising & Communications (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Bernard Slomovitz (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Bernard Slomovitz, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Parties, Parties, Parties. (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Lance Wyman Material (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Lance Wyman Material (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Modern Catering (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Square One Production (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Bay Area Research Project January 1994 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Mexican Museum Miscellaneous Material (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - The Real Multiculturalism: A Struggle for Authority and Power (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Address Book (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Educational Curriculum Guide (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - South Africa in Struggle... A Critical View (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - American Indian Digest 1995 Edition (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Management Project Guide 11/95 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - The Village of Arts and Humanities A Case Study About How Community Organizations Impact Communities Fall 1995 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - governor Gray Davis The First two years a Midterm Review (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Sloan Management Review Fall 1990 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Quick Facts 2000 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Due Process (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous Computer Diskettes (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - High Performance Magazines (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - The Leader's New Work: Building Learning Organizations Manuscript Peter M. Senge Fall 1990 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Sunset Magazine (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - SF Redevelopment Agency (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - SF Redevelopment Agency (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Material (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Mexican Museum Building R.K.F.S. (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - The Mexican Museum Retail Business Plan Nov. 17, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - California Arts Council Material (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - The Mexican Museum Miscellaneous Material (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - The Mexican Museum (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - The Mexican Museum Material (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Directors repeat Transition (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - The Mexican Museum (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - New York Cultivation March 19-22, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - The Mexican Museum Employment & Practices Handbook (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Mexican Museum Material (Box 20, Folder 4-5)
  - Marketing (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Material (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Lorena Garcia Nakata Timesheets (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Case Statement (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Irvine Foundation (Box 20, Folder 10-11)
  - General Mailing List (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Wage Order Guidelines Exempt/Non-Exempt (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Center for the Arts (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Mexican Museum Material (Box 21, Folder 4-6)
  - Mexican Museum Budget Material (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Mexican Museum Catalogs (Box 33, Folder 6)
- National Museum of the American Latino, Federal Commissioner, 2010
  - Final Report to the President and Congress of the U.S. (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - First-Year Report to the President and Congress of the U.S. (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Latino Arts and Cultural Organizations in the U.S. A Historical Survey and Current Assessment (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - A Report to the President and Congress of the U.S. to Illuminate the American Story for all (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - NMAL Commission Mtg Sept. 15, 2010 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Material (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - National Museum of the American Latino Commission (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Material (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - 2010 Alumni Hall of Fame (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Ava 2010 SF,CA Mtg (Home) (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Smithsonian July 12, 2010 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Museums without May 23-26, 2010 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - National Museum of the American Latino Commission (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - LA Commission Meeting/AAM May 20-25 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - NALAC Conference (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Chicago Site Visit-Museum March 23, 2010 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - February 24-26, 2010 NMAL Commission Mtg. Miami, FL (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - National Museum of the American Latino Commission Draft (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Material (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - National Museum of the American Latino Commission (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Material (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Museums Without Borders AAM Meeting & Museum Expo May 23-26, 2010 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Material (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Material (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Mestizo Institute of Culture & Arts (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Wolf Consulting NMAL (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - LORD (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - ALCORTA NAMAL (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Contractor Info (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Contract Review Forms/Criteria NMAL (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Dec. 3-4 NMAL Wash. D.C. Meeting (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Material (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Photograph (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence from Tomas Ybarra-Frausto Oct. 26, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Spanish Colonial Missions (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Chamizal National Memorial (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Quest for Quivira (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Juan Bautista de Anza National Historic Trail (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Gente de Razon - People of the Mission (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Authentic Southwestern Cooking (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous Material (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - NMAL Oct. 13-14 Meeting D.C. (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Denver - NMAL Meeting Oct. 5, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - 874 - Mission Oriented Business Integrated Services (Mobis) (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Denver Service Center Material (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Western National Parks Association 2008-2009 Product Catalog (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Explore Beyond the Shore (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Son de Madera CD (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Panama at the Smithsonian (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Pamphlets (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - From Commissioner Padron + Other 2009 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Arte Latino (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - National Museum of the American Indian Fall 2008 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - May 4, 5, 6th 2011 Federal Commission Mtg. D.C. (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Willful Neglect (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Towards A Shared Vision: U.S. Latinos and the Smithsonian Institution (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - The Time Has Come (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - National Museum and the American Latino Commission - Meeting Sept. 17-19th (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - National Museum of the American Latino Commission Ethics Briefing (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Lorraine Garcia-Nakata Name-tag (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Material (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous CD's (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Hispanic Heritage at the Smithsonian (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Material (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Children's Book Press
  - Children's Book Press Institutional Plan and Operating Budget 2007 and 2009 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - book galley proofs (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Address Books, Daily Planners, Business Cards, 1985 - 2003
  - Various Business Cards (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Lorraine Garcia-Nakata Business Cards/Contact Info 1985-2003 Archive (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - 2013 Calendar (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - 2010 Monthly Planner (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - 2011 Monthly Planner (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - 2014 Calendar (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - 2008 Monthly Planner (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - 2009 Monthly Planner (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - 2007 Monthly Planner (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - 2006 Monthly Planner (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Notebook (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - 2005 Monthly Planner (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - 2004 Monthly Planner (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - 2003 Monthly Planner (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - 2002 Monthly Planner (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - 2001 Monthly Planner (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - 2000 Monthly Planner (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - 1999 Monthly Planner (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - 1997 - 1998 Monthly Planner (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - 1997 Monthly Planner (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - 1996 Monthly Planner (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - 1995 Monthly Planner (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - 1994 Monthly Planner (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - 1993 Monthly Planner (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Achieving Schools Conference 2011 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Contact Book (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - 1992 Appointment and Address Book (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - 1989 Monthly Planner (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Phone Book (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Phone Book (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - 1990-1991 Monthly Planner (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Business Cards/Contact Info. 1985-2003 Archive (Box 32, Folder 5-6)
  - Business Cards/Contact Info. 1985-2003 Archive (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Record Book (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Material (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Media
  - Floppy disks (9) with instructional notes (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - The Fifth Annual California Studies Conference (2 tapes) (Box 34)
  - The Gift of a Story Clarissa Pinkola Estes, Ph.D. (1 tape) (Box 34)
  - Profiles in Arts (7 tapes) (Box 34)
  - Northern Anthology of African American Lit. & Henry Louis Gates, Jr. on Charlie Rose (VHS) (Box 34)
  - 5 Floppy Disks (Box 34)
- Photographs
  - Photos - Mural paintings Lorraine Garcia-Nakata (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Photographs of Lorraine Garcia-Nakata (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Other Material
  - Miscellaneous Catalogs, Reports, Magazines, Daily Planners, etc. (Box 35)
  - Interview magazine Vol.XI no.1 signed by Warhol, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Jose Clemente Orozco - 10 Reproductions of his Mural Paintings (Mexico: Eugenio Fischgrund 1944) (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Cesar Chavez Day proclamation (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Magazine, Catalogs, etc. with Garcia-Nakata (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Family timeline by Kanichi Garcia-Nakata (Box 41, Folder 9)
- LGN art and design
  - Digital Reproductions of Lorraine's Work [color prints] (Box 41, Folder 10, Map-folder 44)
  - Printed items designed by LGN (Box 37, Folder 1)
    Brochures, fliers, etc.
  - posters (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Computer-generated portrait (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - silkscreen posters, some signed (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - artwork (Box 41, Folders 12-13)
- LGN exhibition & event posters
  - LGN exhibition placards (Box 38)
  - Exhibition & event publicity with LGN (Box 37, Folder 6)